<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fragmentation Project</string>
    <string name="question">Magic has been around since 1993. What is the oldest sanctioned magic format that is still played to this day?</string>
    <string name="legacy_answer">Close, Legacy is the second oldest format that is still played. Any card printed in Magic\'s history can be played in Legacy, except for cards that have proven to be too powerful for the format and thus been placed on the ban list. Many people still enjoy playing this to this day. </string>
    <string name="modern_answer">Modern is actually the newest sanctioned magic format. Modern was established as a way to create a new non rotating format inbetween Legacy and Extended. Any card printed from 8th edition and onward is legal, except for those cards that have proven to be too powerful and been place on the ban list.</string>
    <string name="standard_answer">While not the newest format in Magic\'s history, Standard is a rotating format that is always using the newest cards that have been printed. Standard, unlike the other formats rarely bans cards, as cards rotate out of the format whenever newer cards are printed. There have been rare occasions where standard bans have been necessary, but they are few and far between\</string>
    <string name="extended_answer">Extended is a format that is no longer played. Extended was a format that existed before modern that was essentially standard plus cards from a previous few years. The major problem with this format however, was that it was very unpopular amongst players. So much so in fact that it was eventually eliminated with the creation of modern. </string>
    <string name="vintage_answer">Vintage is the oldest format in Magic\s history. This is the format were you can play any card ever printed, the only exceptions are that you can only play one of each card on the Restricted list and cards that have to deal with Ante or Dexterity are banned for tournament reasons.  </string>
</resources>
